You're cute, Ikemon.
かわいいね、イケモン
copper?
どう?
fine?
元気?
I'm fine.
元気です
I'm sorry, actually.
ごめんね、本当は
It's totally okay.
全然大丈夫
Aren't you angry?
怒ってない?
You're not angry.
怒ってないね
Together, with someone, with everything,
一緒にね、誰かがね、 いろいろね、
My grandmother used to eat it.
おばあ食べたりしたもんね
Yes, I ate it.
はい、食べましたね
Has the rice cake melted?
おかやは溶けたんですか?
Yes, it melted.
はい、溶けました
TRUE?
本当?
Did something good happen?
なんか、いいことあった?
there was.
ありました
What is it?
なんですか?
Since then, I have appeared on BS TV,
あれから、 BSのテレビにも出れて、
I'm so glad that my grandma saw it.
おばあちゃんが 見てくださって 本当に
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
I'm grateful.
感謝 してます
I got out, after all.
出れたんだ、結局
Good for you.
よかったね
He watched TV.
テレビ見てくれたんだ
You said it was a dream.
夢だって言ってたもんね
Yes, it's a dream.
はい、夢です
What do you want to do from now on?
これからどうしていきたい?
From now on, I want to appear on TV more.
これからは、もっと テレビに 出たいです
yes?
そう?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Do you want to do gravure?
グラビアをやっていきたいの?
yes.
はい
I want to become a gravure idol.
グラビアアイドルになりたいです
Can I ask you a simple story one more time?
もう一回、簡単な 話を聞いてもいい?
yes.
はい
How old are you now?
今、歳は?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
You're young.
若いね
You came to Tokyo.
上京してきたのね
yes.
はい
I came to Tokyo from Kagoshima.
鹿児島から上京してきたの
Have you been to Tokyo?
東京とか行ったの?
yes.
はい
They will support you.
応 援してくれるんだよね
I agree.
そうですね
They will support you.
応援してくれる
What will happen now when you return?
帰ったら、今、 どうなる?
I'm thinking of going back during summer vacation.
夏休みには帰ろうと思って
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏はいるんだっけ?
I'm here.
います
Are you in touch?
連絡とってる?
I'm taking it.
とってます
Can you call me?
電話とかして?
Do you call about 3 times a week?
電話は 週3回ぐらいですか?
That's quite a lot.
結構するね
yes.
はい
My boyfriend has such a cute girlfriend,
彼氏さんはこんなかわいい彼女ってさ、
From a distance.
遠距離でね
Are you worried about fluffiness?
ふわきの心配とかしてない?
No, that's right.
いや、 そうですね
Do you have it?
ありますか?
do.
して
hey.
ね
Do you make it fluffy?
ふわきとかするの?
I don't.
しないです
do not?
しない?
Isn't it with me?
俺とのわけじゃない?
different?
違う?
It doesn't make any sense.
意味がないんで
I agree.
そうですね
Is it a gray area?
グレーゾーンですか?
Gray zone?
グレーゾーン?
yes.
はい
You say you want to try something like Papakatsu, right?
パパカツみたいにやってみたいって言ってるでしょ?
yes.
はい
That's what I said.
言ってました
Haven't you done that yet?
そういうのはさ、 まだやってない?
I haven't done it yet.
まだしてないです
That's it.
そういうのです
When I meet my dad and others.
パパとかと会うと
We need to make the physical relationships similar.
体の関係を似せないと
What should I do about that?
そうなのどうするの?
I might refuse.
断るかもです
physical relationships.
体の関係
turn down?
断る?
yes.
はい
Because my boyfriend is important.
彼氏が大切なので
On the other hand, I was worried about my boyfriend cheating on me.
逆に彼氏の浮気心配したりしてね
I do it because it's long distance.
遠距離なのでします
Hey.
ねえ
Are you worried?
心配になるでしょ?
Yes, I'm worried
はい、心配
is.
です
Yes, I believe it.
はい、 信じてます
Did your boyfriend watch TV?
彼氏テレビ見てくれたの?
My boyfriend also watched it.
彼氏も見てくれました
Did you say something?
何か言ってた?
He complimented me and said it was amazing.
すごいって褒めてくれました
TRUE?
本当?
That was good.
良かったね
My favorite egg is...
好きな卵は...
Do you think?
おもやす?
yes.
はい
Why do you like Omoyasu?
なんでおもやす好きなの?
After all, the combination of eggs and rice is the best.
やっぱり卵と ライスの 組み合わせって 最高なんで
I like it the most.
一番好きです
I know a restaurant that is really delicious.
すごい美味しい おもやすの店知ってるよ
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
I want to go.
行きたいです
Well then, today...
じゃあさ、 今日はさ、
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
I'm sorry.
ご めんね
No, it's okay.
いやいや、大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
Was it scary?
怖かった?
That's right.
そうだよね
It was scary, wasn't it?
怖かったよね
It was scary.
怖かったね
Someone was there, right?
誰かいたよね?
is that so?
そうですか?
Who could it be?
誰だろう?
Not told?
言われない?
It's not said.
言われないですね
What?
なんだ?
Why do I want to do it?
なぜなぜしたくなっちゃう?
what happened?
どうしたの?
no...
いや...
It's squishy.
ぷにぷにだね
It's cool to put out something like this.
こんなこと出してる 格好するんだ
Yes, I will.
はい、します
It's summer after all.
夏だしね
I agree.
そうですね
I got a summer look.
夏の格好できました
Hey, this is it. This is a string. What kind of string is this?
ちょっとこれさ、 これ、紐、 何の紐?
It's underwear.
下着です
Is it okay if I take this out?
これ出しちゃっていいの?
picture?
え?
I don't know.
分からない
I don't know?
分からない?
If you want to do your best in the entertainment industry, study passion.
ちゃんとさ、これからもさ、 芸能を頑張るなら パッションを勉
I have to be strong.
強 しないと
I agree.
そうですね
It suits you though.
似合ってるけどね
You're keeping it beautiful.
綺麗にしてるね
That's amazing, it's a naughty chew.
すごいさ、 エッチなチューするね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do you like chew?
チュー好き?
yes.
はい
I couldn't do it at all during this time.
この間全然できなかったけどね
Because I didn't like it.
イヤいしちゃったから
Do you really like it?
本当は好きなんだ?
no...
いや...
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いよ
This is actually what I wanted to photograph.
本当はこういうのがさ、 撮りたかったんだよね
During this time.
この間
It's cute.
可愛いね
How many cups?
何カップだっけ?
Like this?
こんな?
amazing.
すごい
Do this right now, dress like this so I can show you.
これすぐこうやってさ、 見せられるように こういう服にな
Are you saying that?
ってる の?
Hmm.
うーん
That's right.
そうなんですよね
It's a fulllander, right?
フルランダーでしょ
No, no.
いやいや
Just do it yourself, this.
ちょっと自分でさ、これ
Use your chest, your chest.
胸、胸元さ、使って
Are you going to show me?
見せてくの?
This is short.
これは短いね
Flavia's practice.
フラビアの練習
I want to be buried there.
埋もれたい、そこに
There's someone you admire.
憧れの人がいるんだよね
yes.
はい
My only love.
私のだけ愛さんです
It's a little similar.
ちょっと似てるもんね
Things like body shape.
体型とか
I'm aiming for it.
目指してます
do your best.
頑張って
Erotic, erotic, plump.
エロ、 エロロリブチ、 ムチムチ系
Are you taking good care of yourself?
ちゃんと気使ってんの?
alias.
別名
A little good.
少しいい
Is it a little good?
少しいい?
What kind of things are you doing?
どんなことやってんの?
I agree.
そうですね
It's like applying oil.
オイル塗ったりって感じで
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Do you apply it every day?
毎日塗ってんの?
I agree.
そうですね
I'll paint it next time.
今度塗ってあげる
I'll paint it.
塗ってあげる
I'll go out to paint and play.
塗りに、 遊びに行ってあげるよ、
Now.
今で
You're happy, aren't you?
嬉しいでしょ
Are you having a little trouble?
ちょっと困っちゃう?
I might give up my legs.
足あげちゃうかもしれない
fault.
あら
Doing naughty poses.
エッチなポーズしてる
strange.
おかしい
I have to do poses like this.
こういうポーズもしなきゃいけないし
I have to do a sexy pose.
セクシーなポーズしなきゃいけない
It was hot today, wasn't it?
今日暑かったでしょ?
Yes, it was hot.
はい、暑かった
Because it was hot.
暑かったから
I agree.
そうですね
You haven't taken a bath yet, have you?
まだお風呂入ってないでしょ?
It's not included.
入 ってないです
Well then, a lot
じゃあいっぱい
difference.
さ
Shall we go to sleep?
寝 ちゃおうか
Isn't this connected?
これ繋がってるんじゃないの?
Which is more difficult?
どっちが難しい?
From tomorrow?
明日から?
You can touch this all the time.
ずっと触ってられるね、これ
What do you think?
どうですか?
Infinite nothingness.
無限無に無にだね
Do you want it at home?
家に欲しい?
Infinite nothingness.
無限無に無に
Your boyfriend also touches this, right?
彼氏もこれ触るでしょ?
yes.
はい
Have you forgiven me yet?
もう心許してくれたの?
yes.
はい
So, is it okay to be my boyfriend?
じゃあ彼氏でいいですか?
That's tough.
厳しいね
strict?
厳しい?
So what about your second boyfriend?
じゃあ第2の彼氏は?
About 10th.
第10くらい
yes.
はい
I'll kill the 9th one.
9番目は 抹殺するわ
scared?
怖い?
I have to say hello.
挨拶しないと
Why do you hide it?
なんで隠すの?
I have to look at the camera.
カメラ舐めないといけないじゃん
I'm sweating.
汗かいてる
picture?
え?
I'll feed you omoresu.
オモレス食べさせてあげる
You like eating, right?
食べるの好きでしょ?
Yes, I like it.
はい、好きです
It's so sticky.
ムチムチだもんね
now?
今更?
difficult?
難しい?
Isn't it difficult?
難しくないの?
I haven't heard it.
聞いてない
You look great.
すごい格好してるね